Новый санскритско-русский словарь.
Ефимовский С. В.; Торус Пресс, 2012.
--------------------------------------------------

INDICORPUS-31 (корпус словарей для Lingvo-x3):
https://www.mediafire.com/file/h5v13sbnah8g4l8

Sanskrit declension (361160 tables + index 4.2 M).
Ṛgveda (based on ed. Th. Aufrecht).
Ṛgveda commentary by S.W. Jamison & J.P. Brereton.
Mahābhārata-Saṁhitā (based on ed. Sukthankar).
Vālmīki-Rāmāyaṇa (based on critical ed. G.H. Bhatt).
Word-to-Word Vālmīki-Rāmāyaṇa dictionary (beta! version).
The Pali Text Society's Pali-English Dictionary. T.W. Rhys Davids & William Stede.
Pandanus Database of Sanskrit, Prakrit, Hindi, Bengali, Tamil, Malayalam, English and Latin Plant names.
Dhātupāṭha index. Pāṇini
Sanskrit conjugation (2600 verbs tables + index).
Index to the Names in the Mahabharata. Søren Sørensen.
Симфонический санскритско-русский толковый словарь Махабхараты. Б.Л. Смирнов.
Dictionary of the Vedic rituals based on the Śrauta and Gŗhya sutras. Citrabhānu Sen.
Sanskrit-English Dictionary by Monier-Williams; 1899.
The practical Sanskrit-English dictionary. V.S. Apte, P.K. Gode, C.G. Karve, revised edition; 1957.
A Sanskrit-English dictionary by Arthur Anthony Macdonell.
Śabda-kalpadrumah or an encyclopedic dictionary of Sanskrit words. Rādhākāntadeva, Vasu, V., & Vasu, H.; 1886.
Vedic index of names & subjects by Arthur Anthony Macdonell.
Indian Epigraphical Glossary by D.C. Sircar.
Sanskrit names of plants and their botanical equivalents; Gerrit Jan. Mulenbeld; 1988.
Buddhist Hybrid Sanskrit Grammar and Dictionary by Franklin Edgerton (vol 2: dictionary).
Vettam Mani's Purānic Encyclopaedia.
The Purāṇa Index by V.R. Ramachandra Dikshitar.
Mahābhārata — cultural index.
Tamil lexicon. University of Madras; 1924-1936.
Concise Pali-English Dictionary by A.P. Buddhadatta Mahathera.
Краткий пали-русский словарь. Д.А. Ивахненко, А. Гунский.
Sanskrit-Russian Dictionary; 28555 words.
Sanskrit-English Word for Word translations.
Bengali&Sanskrit-English Word for Word translations.
The Bhaktivedanta Encyclopedia.